contribs.org 2017-04-22

# SME Server:Privacy policy - SME Server

Privacy policy Valid from 8 February 2016 

Your privacy matters to us. This policy outlines the information we collect from you — and what we do with it. 

Koozali Inc. collects personal information from you in a number of different ways. For example, when you download one of our products, receive services from us or use one of our websites (including www.contribs.org and www.koozali.org). 

At Koozali Inc., we consider your privacy to be extremely important to us. These are the fundamental principles that we follow in relation to your personal information: 

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. 
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to provide you with services, products, to comply with the law, or to protect our rights. 
  * We don’t store personal information unless required for the on-going operation of services to you, to provide you with products, to comply with law or to protect our rights. 
  * We will use personal information that you provide to us in accordance with this privacy policy. 

**What we collect**

We may collect the following types of personal information from you: 

_Websites_

When you register to use certain parts of our websites, such as wikis, bugtracker or forums, or register for free accounts, we may ask for personal information such as your full name, email address and a password. 

_Forums and mailinglists_

These are available to our community. Any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information and may be recorded, archived and republished by anyone. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information in such areas. 

When you register for services from Koozali Inc. (Including donations), we may ask for information such as your email address, billing address, and credit card information. Credit card information is only used in processing your transaction. Please note that we may use a third party payment processing merchant to process your payments. 

_Non-personally identifying information_

Koozali Inc. may collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor’s request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use our websites and services. 

_General_

If you contact us and provide us with information, we may keep a record of that correspondence and information
